<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Floating Overlay</string>

    <!-- Main activity strings -->
    <string name="main_instructions_heading">How to Use</string>
    <string name="main_instructions_text">
        This application will display a floating overlay with controls that allow changing the system
        volume. The application uses a foreground task to show the overlay, and can be closed by
        pressing the exit button on the overlay itself, or by using the close action of the persistent
        foreground service notification.
        \n\n
        To show the overlay, press the show overlay button.
    </string>

    <!-- Permissions activity strings -->
    <string name="perm_req_heading">Permission Required</string>
    <string name="perm_req_message">
        This app requires extra permissions to be able to run. If the permissions are not granted
        the application will not work on your device.
    </string>
    <string name="perm_req_modify_btn">Grant Permission</string>

    <string name="perm_req_notify">Display Persistent Notification</string>
    <string name="perm_req_notify_msg">
        The application shows a persistent notification while the overlay is visible.
    </string>
    <string name="perm_granted_notify_msg">
        You have granted the notification permission! The application will use this permission
        to shows a persistent notification while the overlay is visible.
    </string>

    <string name="perm_req_foreground">Foreground Service</string>
    <string name="perm_req_foreground_msg">
        The application uses a foreground service to display a floating overlay with controls.
    </string>
    <string name="perm_granted_foreground_msg">
        You have granted the foreground service permission! The application uses a foreground
        service to display a floating overlay with controls.
    </string>

    <string name="perm_req_overlay">Draw Over Other Apps</string>
    <string name="perm_req_overlay_msg">
        The application will draw an overlay with controls over other applications.
    </string>
    <string name="perm_granted_overlay_msg">
        You have granted the draw over other apps permission! The application will draw an overlay
        with controls over other applications.
    </string>

    <string name="perm_req_exit_msg">If you wish to close the application please press the back button.</string>
</resources>